camtogays.com 2018-09-30

# PRIVACY POLICY

## By accessing and using our Sites, you signify your assent to this privacy policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use camtogays.com

camtogays.com preserves the right to modify or to adapt the pages of the website camtogays.com or its privacy police at any time. These modifications shall become enforceable from the moment of their publication on the website camtogays.com. By continuing to use the website camtogays.com, the user accepts these modifications. The user should therefore read the version of these privacy police available online at the moment. The users presence on the website implies his/her full acceptance of any modification or adaptation.

## Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail : contact@camtogays.com

## Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we [camtogays.com] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Registration and Order Forms

In order to gain access to our Site, you may be requested to provide us with your date of birth. In addition, in order to purchase goods and services from our Sites, or to become a member of our Sites, a user must complete the on-line registration/order form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include your name, mailing address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address). If we have trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

## Use of third-party cookies

Within the commercial use of the website camtogays.com, third parties can place and read cookies on the users browser, as well as use web tags in order to collect information for placing advertising on camtogays.com.  
The user can disable third-party cookies by modifying his/her browser settings. A tutorial to allow users to manage third-party cookies is available here:  
<http://www.bobulous.org.uk/misc/third-party-cookies.html>  
[http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)  
The user of camtogays.com explicitly allows third parties to process his/her personal data in the conditions and for the purposes described above.

## Profiling

From time to time, we may combine personal information and preferences collected on-line with personal information and preferences collected off-line in order to enhance and personalize our services.

## Security

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure.camtogays.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to camtogays.com and you do so at your own risk.

## Children

Collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit.

## Opt-in and user communication

Subscriber's expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter or disclosed to third-parties.

## Opt-out and user communication

Subscriber's expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, other offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the offer) then the site may transfer the subscriber's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider.

## Your Right

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section. If you have additional questions then please write to us at contact@camtogays.com
